Today is a day of short celebration. We
have a lot of challenges ahead of us,
but I'm very very confident with this
group of people and the dedication and
hard work that we've seen from everybody
in
[Music]
here. I could guide in the dark. I see
you calling my name. I hear you
shouting, hear you calling, but it's not
the same. Every weapon you are throwing
right into my back. Doesn't matter to me
cuz I'm keeping my track. Let me
go. Let me
go. Stop talking. Let me
[Music]
go. Our turn together always ended up in
war. Every whisper made you jealous and
from the start. It is nice to see you
shouting out for throwing me out. No
excuses by the sun. It's going to be the
last. Let me
go. Let me
go. Oh, baby. Let me go.
[Music]
Now I go out in the dark smiling back at
your face with a nice and cozy feeling
after leaving your place. This road will
lead me somewhere I don't really know
but it's someone
always let me
go let me
go let me go. This is the first one. the
first truly truly truly 100%
defining. Um we're going to create
something unique and special. Um and I
really do think we have a team and a
philosophy and a vision to change life
insurance uh in the
Philippines.
We are 70 strong effort Philippines and
the
realization and the realization of the
vision has started. All right. I'd like
to then propose a toast to the great
success of FWD and to changing the way
consumers feel about insurance. Cheers.
Feeling after leaving your place.
There's hope leaving me somewhere. I
don't really know, but it's almost
someone
always. Let me
go. Let me
go. Oh, baby. Let me go.
[Music]